Register of the Chinese National Relief and Rehabilitation Administration photograph negatives
Hoover Institution Archives
- Photographic Negatives, 1946-1947 (Boxes 1-4)
  - Henan (Honan), photographer Larry Gahn (1493-1499), 1947 April 11 (Box 3)
  - Zhengzhou (Chengchow), photographer Larry Gahn (1500-1506), 1947 April 12 (Box 3)
  - Huaiyuan, photographer Larry Gahn (1507-1512), 1947 April 18 (Box 3)
  - Henan (Honan), photographer Larry Gahn (1513-1515), 1947 April 11 (Box 3)
  - Unidentified (1516) (Box 3)
  - Zhengzhou (Chengchow), photographer Larry Gahn (1517), 1947 April 12 (Box 3)
  - Henan (Honan), photographer Larry Gahn (1518-1520, 1519 is missing), 1947 April 17 (Box 3)
  - Nandao (Nantao), photographer Warren Lee (1521-1530), 1947 April 30 (Box 3)
  - Hangzhou (Hangchow), photographer Dick Wilson (1531-1548), 1947 May 4-10 (Box 3)
  - Zhoushan Qundao (Chusan Island), photographer C. M. Chao (1549-1591, 1574 is missing), 1947 May 8-11 (Box 3)
  - Shanghai, photographer Warren Lee (1592-1599), 1947 May 13 (Box 3)
  - Shanghai, photographer Warren Lee (1600-1602), 1947 May 13 (Box 3)
  - Hangzhou (Hangchow), photographer Dick Wilson (1603-1637), 1947 May 8-10 (Box 3)
  - Hangzhou (Hangchow), photographer Dick Wilson (1638-1656), 1947 May 8-10 (Box 4)
  - Shanghai, photographer Larry Gahn (1657-1667), 1947 May 17 (Box 4)
  - Shanghai, photographer Warren Lee (1668-1670), 1947 May 21 (Box 4)
  - Jiangwan (Kiangwan), photographer Warren Lee (1671-1706), 1947 May 26 (Box 4)
  - Point Island, photographer Warren Lee (1707-1710), 1947 June 5 (Box 4)
  - Point Island, photographer Warren Lee (1711-1722), 1947 June 3 (Box 4)
  - Jiangwan (Kiangwan), photographer Warren Lee (1723-1729), 1947 June 4 (Box 4)
  - Jiangwan (Kiangwan), photographer Warren Lee (1730-1731), 1947 June 5 (Box 4)
  - Shanghai, photographer Warren Lee (1732-1733), 1947 June 5 (Box 4)
  - Shanghai, photographer Warren Lee (1734-1739), 1947 June 10 (Box 4)
  - Point Island, photographer Warren Lee (1740-1748), 1947 June 12 (Box 4)
  - Shanghai Wharf, photographer Warren Lee (1749-1755), 1947 June 13 (Box 4)
  - Point Island, photographer Warren Lee (1756-1773), 1947 June 12 (Box 4)
  - Changtu Dao, Zhoushan Qundao, photographer Warren Lee (1774-1780), 1947 June 14-17 (Box 4)
  - Shenjia Men, Zhoushan Qundao (Chusan Island), photographer Warren Lee (1781-1785), 1947 June 14-17 (Box 4)
  - Putuo Shan, Zhoushan Qundao (Chusan Island), photographer Warren Lee (1786-1789), 1947 June 14-17 (Box 4)
  - Zhoushan Qundao (Chusan Island), photographer Warren Lee (1790-1807, 1803-1804 missing), 1947 June 14-17 (Box 4)
  - Zhoushan Qundao (Chusan Island), photographer Dick Wilson (1808-1818), 1947 June 14-17 (Box 4)
  - Point Island, photographer C. M. Chao (1819-1827, 1827 is missing), 1947 July 4 (Box 4)
  - Flooded Area at West River, photographer Warren Lee (1828-1829), 1947 July 2-8 (Box 4)
  - Shilong, Guangdong (Kwangtung), photographer Warren Lee (1830-1831), 1947 July 2-8 (Box 4)
  - Lubao, Guangdong (Kwangtung), photographer Warren Lee (1832-1844), 1947 July 2-8 (Box 4)
  - Shunde, Guangdong (Kwangtung), photographer Warren Lee (1845-1862), 1947 July 2-8 (Box 4)
  - Foshan, Guangdong (Kwangtung), photographer Warren Lee (1863), 1947 July 2-8 (Box 4)
  - Sanshui, Guangdong (Kwangtung), photographer Warren Lee (1864-1872), 1947 July 2-8 (Box 4)
  - Foshan, Guangdong (Kwangtung), photographer Warren Lee (1873-1882), 1947 July 2-8 (Box 4)
  - Sanshui, Zaogang, Guangdong (Kwangtung), photographer Warren Lee (1883-1897), 1947 July 2-8 (Box 4)
  - Flooded Area near West River, photographer Warren Lee (1898-1903), 1947 July 2-8 (Box 4)
  - Guangzhou (Canton) Guangdong (Kwangtung), photographer Warren Lee (1904-1910), 1947 July 2-8 (Box 4)
  - Guangzhou (Canton), photographer Warren Lee (1911-1933, 1931 is missing), 1947 July 2-8 (Box 4)
  - Unidentified (1934-1942), undated (Box 4)
  - Hongqiao (Hujao) Airfield, CAT, photographer Warren Lee (1943-1944), 1947 July 16 (Box 4)
  - Shanghai, photographer Warren Lee (1945-1960, 1949 is missing; sleeve notes indicate that 1949 and 1954 are the same), 1947 July 31 (Box 4)
  - CNRRA office, photographer Warren Lee (1960A, 1961), 1947 August 2 (Box 4)
  - Shanghai, photographer Warren Lee (1962-1970), 1947 August 8 (Box 4)
  - Point Island, photographer Warren Lee (1971-1973), 1947 August 20 (Box 4)
  - Chenzhu (Chenju), photographer Warren Lee (1974-1975), 1947 August 22 (Box 4)
  - Huangpu (Whangpoo), photographer Warren Lee (1976), 1947 June (Box 4)
  - Chenzhu (Chenju), photographer Warren Lee (1977-1979), 1947 August 22 (Box 4)
  - Chenzhu (Chenju), photographer Warren Lee (1980-1987), 1947 August 20 (Box 4)
  - Huangpu (Whangpoo), photographer Warren Lee (1988-1995), 1947 June (Box 4)
  - CNRRA office, photographer Warren Lee (1996-1998), 1947 August 29 (Box 4)
  - Point Island, photographer Warren Lee (1999-2001), 1947 September 2 (Box 4)
  - Shanghai Wharf, photographer Warren Lee (2002-2027), 1947 September 8 (Box 4)
  - Point Island, photographer Warren Lee (2028-2043), 1947 September 12 (Box 4)
  - Point Island, photographer Warren Lee (2044-2050), 1947 September 22 (Box 4)
  - Point Island, photographer Warren Lee (2051-2054), 1947 September (Box 4)
  - Unidentified subject, unknown photographer (2055-2229, 2124, 2128, 2132, 2134-2136, 2138, and 2142 had numbered sleeves, but no negatives were enclosed), undated (Box 4)
- Original Negative Sleeves, 1946-1947 (Boxes 5-7)
  Arranged numerically by negative number, 0001-2229, with gaps. Note that these sleeves, which originally held the negatives found in boxes 1-4, are now empty.
  - Envelopes bearing original descriptive data and number (0001-0700) (Box 5)
  - Envelopes bearing original descriptive data and number (0701-1398) (Box 6)
  - Envelopes bearing original descriptive data and number (1399-2229) (Box 7)